<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>ROSEdu News</title>
 <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/rss.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/"/>
 <updated>2013-12-16T19:47:55+02:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.rosedu.org</id>
 <author>
   <name>ROSEdu</name>
   <email>contact@rosedu.org</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Firefox OS App Days</title>
   <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/en/2013/01/13/firefox-os-app-days/"/>
   <updated>2013-01-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id></id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, the 26th of January 2013, we invite you to &lt;a href='http://firefoxosappdaybucharest.eventbrite.com/#'&gt;Firefox OS App Days&lt;/a&gt;. Firefox OS App Days is an event dedicated to web apps; we welcome you to join Mozilla in launching its new operating system &lt;a href='http://firefoxosappdaybucharest.eventbrite.com/#'&gt;Firefox OS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please bring your laptops, mobile devices and apps you would like to show or ideas for apps you would like to build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firefox App Days will take place at &lt;a href='http://bucharest.the-hub.net/'&gt;The Hub&lt;/a&gt;. We invite everyone passionate about technology, especially web technologies, to come and share their input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please fill the &lt;a href='http://firefoxosappdaybucharest.eventbrite.com/#'&gt;Eventbrite Form&lt;/a&gt; if you intend to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>RSoC 2012 Launch</title>
   <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/en/2012/04/23/rsoc-launch/"/>
   <updated>2012-04-23T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id></id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 2012 ROSEdu Summer of Code has started!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the summer, eight students will contribute to an Open Source projects, while being guided along the way by members of the project&amp;#8217;s community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the participants will be granted a 1000 euro scholarship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, the proposed projects are Webkit, Apache HBase, Dexonline, WoUSO, vmchecker and WHC, but there are more to come!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to spend your summer contributing to an interesting Open Source project while learning new things and earning a bit of cash, be sure to join us Thursday, the 26th of April, at 14:00, at the Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Science, room EC004, for the official launch of the 2012 ROSEdu Summer of Code program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://soc.rosedu.org/2012/'&gt;http://soc.rosedu.org/2012/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Geek Power</title>
   <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/en/2011/04/10/geek-power/"/>
   <updated>2011-04-10T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id></id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Do you like writing code? Do you like working together with other programmers? Are words like commit, debugging, IDE, malloc, threads part of your vocabulary?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If so, we invite you to participate on the 16th-17th of April 2011 weekend to one of the coolest hacking events&lt;span&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to develop one of your own ideas or to work on an older project that you didn’t have time to work on or just want to work in a team, then this event is for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will get to meet business people, as well as other people that are passionate about hacking with whom you can discuss your ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please confirm your participation here&lt;span&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; and come Saturday, 16th of April, at the Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Science, room EG106 (for hacking we will use EG207, EG306 and EG405).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event is organized by the Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Science, ROSEdu and Cronian Labs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://geekpower.eventbrite.com/'&gt;http://geekpower.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hackathon</title>
   <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/en/2011/03/23/hackathon/"/>
   <updated>2011-03-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id></id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This weekend (26.03.2011) we will hold a 12 hour Hackaton, starting Saturday at 6PM till Sunday morning (6AM).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started this event with the idea that WoUSO developers should get toghether and do some real hacking. Now, we will hold a general hacking event, where everyone is invited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to participate just register yourself here &lt;span&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;. You can hack whatever you want. We also decided that every participant should put in a small amunt of money for pizza and drinks (20 RON). The event will take place in EG306 room in Politehnica Campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need directions just ask on rosedu mailing list or on IRC: #rosedu on freenode. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.doodle.com/w4xr55sycmm3y5fq'&gt;http://www.doodle.com/w4xr55sycmm3y5fq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>CDL v3.0</title>
   <link href="http://www.rosedu.org/en/2011/03/22/cdl-v3/"/>
   <updated>2011-03-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id></id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 3rd edition of the Open Source Community and Development Lab (CDL) has started for several weeks! We are happy to have such enthusiast students and mentors working hard to make this the best edition of CDL so far!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, the students attented 5 courses with hackaton session for the last five weeks, and we still have four more weeks to go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special invited guests will talk about careers in software engineering, system administration, network administration, open source software communities and tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out more about who our students are, what they&amp;#8217;re doing, on &lt;a href='http://cdl.rosedu.org'&gt;http://cdl.rosedu.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
